upfluence.com 2016-12-02

# Privacy policy - Upfluence

## PRIVACY POLICY

## UPDATED August 31st, 2015

The following details our privacy Policy (the “Policy”) at UPFLUENCE Inc (UFPLUENCE) and describes the types of information we gather from those persons visiting the Internet websites upfluence.com, publishr.io, and reachr.io (the “Site(s)”) and how we use such information. We understand the importance of privacy and accordingly, treat all information received in a responsible manner. This Policy applies to all of the services offered by UPFLUENCE (the “services”) on the Sites. By accessing the Sites, you agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Sites. Each time you use the Sites, the current version of the Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, when you use the Sites, you should check the date of this Policy (which appears at the top) and review any changes since the last version.

## USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY UPFLUENCE

UPFLUENCE may collect two types of information from users of our Sites: “personal information” (such as name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, etc.) and “aggregate information” (such as frequency of visits to any of the Sites, search terms entered, Site pages most frequently accessed, browser type, etc.) We use this information in an effort to improve your experience on the Sites and to communicate with you about information that you request. We may also use this information to help us target specific services or offers to you, to help us develop and improve our Sites, and to tailor our Sites to your interests.

## COLLECTING AND USING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

UPFLUENCE only collects personal information that is voluntarily provided when users sign up for an UPFLUENCE site. We ask you for personal information such as your name, address, email address, and social security number. (Please note that we require social security numbers for income tax reporting purposes.) We may also request PayPal payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers.

## COLLECTING AND USING YOUR AGGREGATE INFORMATION

UPFLUENCE also collects aggregate information, which is non-personally identifiable information about you, such as frequency of visits to the Sites, search terms entered, browser type, etc. Aggregate information is used in a collective manner, and no single person can be identified by that compiled information. UPFLUENCE uses aggregate information to provide its services and remuneration, as well as to determine the use of our Sites and to monitor, audit and analyze information pertaining to our business metrics.

## SHARING, SELLING AND TRADING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED ONLINE WITH THIRD PARTIES

UPFLUENCE shares personal information with our parents and subsidiaries, and on occasion, we may share personal information with third party service providers, such as credit card processing companies. These third party service providers are not authorized to retain, share, store or use your personal information for any purposes other than to provide the services for which they have been hired to provide. In addition, in order to protect against potential fraud, we may verify with third parties the personal information you provide when you sign up for a PayPerPost account. In the course of such verification, we may receive personal information about you. We do not sell, trade or otherwise share your personal information with unrelated third parties for their own marketing purposes.

Given the nature of UPFLUENCE’s website, information willingly provided by the influencers (blog writers, social media users and any other user who registered as an influencer) will be shared with advertisers (any user registered as an advertiser on the websites) in order to ease the selection process.

In following circumstances, UPFLUENCE may elect to share or transfer your personal information to unrelated third parties: (i) to comply with a legal requirement, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on UPFLUENCE, (ii) to investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; (iii) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of UPFLUENCE; (iv) when we believe it is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of UPFLUENCE or other persons, or (v) as otherwise required or permitted by law.

Sharing, Selling and Trading Aggregate Information Collected Online with Third Parties We may share, sell or trade with third parties aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. As stated earlier, such information does not identify you individually.

## COOKIES

Cookies are pieces of information which websites transfer to your computer’s web browser for storage on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit the Sites, we may place one or more cookies on your computer to uniquely identify your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people blog. We store minimal personal information in cookies and protect this information. We do not store complete records or credit card numbers in cookies. You may chose to set your computer to not accept cookies, but some features and services on the Sites may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

## USE OF PIXEL TAGS/CLEAR GIFS/WEB BEACONS

A pixel tag, also known as a clear GIF or web beacon, is an invisible tag placed on articles or other editorial content created on UPFLUENCE but not on your computer. When you access these pages, pixel tags generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous website visit.

## SECURITY PERTAINING TO YOUR INFORMATION

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. UPFLUENCE employees can access personal information, service providers and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. We use secure socket layer (“SSL”) technology to encrypt and protect the security of your personal information, including but not limited to your credit card number, when it is sent over the Internet. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. IN NO EVENT WILL UPFLUENCE OR SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES OR ANY PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DELIVERING THE SITES BE LIABLE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER FOR ANY DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS, USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITES, OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY FAILURE OR PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE (INCLUDING LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION OR DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, AND DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM INACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION OR INCONVENIENCE, DELAY, OR LOSS OF THE USE OF THE SITES). THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS APPLY WHETHER THE ALLEGED LIABILITY IS BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER BASIS, EVEN IF UPFLUENCE OR ITS AFFILIATES OR ANY OTHER PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

## INTEGRITY OF YOUR DATA

UPFLUENCE processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

## COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT/DMCA NOTICE

If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof and believe that any submission on the Sites or any other content on the Sites infringes upon your copyrights, you may submit a notification pursuant to our Offices in Delaware, Switzerland, or France.

(i) A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;

(ii) Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;

(iii) Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material;

(iv) Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail;

(v) A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;

(vi) A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

UPFLUENCE receives notifications of claimed infringement on the following email address: team@publishr.io or rue de Monthoux, 49 - 1201 Geneva Switzerland. Only DMCA notices should go to this address; any other comments, requests, or other communications should be directed to hey@publishr.io. You acknowledge that if you fail to comply with all of the requirements of this Section, your DMCA notice may not be valid.

## CHILDREN AND PRIVACY

Our Sites are not directed to children and we will not request personally identifiable information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 18, unless we have obtained verifiable parental consent from a parent or legal guardian. If we become aware that a user under the age of 13 has registered with any of our Sites, provided personally identifiable information, and UPFLUENCE has not obtained prior verifiable consent from a parent or legal guardian, we will immediately remove the user’s personally identifiable information from our files.

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

The Sites may contain links to websites operated by other people or companies. Those websites may have their own privacy policy or no privacy policy at all. UPFLUENCE does not have any responsibility for those websites, and we provide the links solely for the convenience of our visitors.

## BUSINESS TRANSFERS

In the event that UPFLUENCE sells substantially all of its assets, or one of UPFLUENCE’s business units is acquired, personally identifiable information of visitors to the Sites and aggregate information will likely be one of the transferred assets.

## CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Please note that we may change this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy on our Sites.

## CORRECTIONS/INFORMATION REMOVAL/OPT-OUT

If your name, e-mail or postal address, telephone number or other personal information changes, you may update, correct or omit the irrelevant information by contacting us at UPFLUENCE rue de Monthoux 49, 1201 Geneva Switzerland or by visiting our site and clicking Contact. If you prefer not to receive newsletters or other marketing e-mails from UPFLUENCE, please let us know by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any newsletter or marketing e-mail you receive. If you prefer not to receive marketing mail via the mail carrier, please let us know by sending a request to: UPFLUENCE, rue de monthoux 49, 1201 Geneva Switzerland. Please be sure to include in any e-mail or postal mail, your full name, e-mail address, postal address, and any message. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) days to become effective.

## CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through the Sites or at Privacy Policy Concerns Coordinator on team@upfluence.com
